So friends, ICC Prudential Life
Insurance Company's numbers have been disclosed,
so let's see what is
inside the numbers of quarter one, but first of all, tell me that
according to me,
this is the first company of the sector of life insurance company, it is going to disclose its numbers, so a lot is going to
depend on the
market mood and behavior, let's see the data, the
data is given in the lab, I will
convert it and explain it to you friend, please
look at it carefully because the
data of life insurance company is
a bit complex, so
I will try to understand it a little better, please
look at it carefully, if we talk about the previous quantity, then the
total income of the company in the last quarter is in
loss to you or this is what I am seeing
in the preview, let me understand in the
big picture of the last quarter,
today on 490, if the company had generated total income
of 140061 last year, did the company have a
loss, whereas in automatic mode, the
total income of the company is
around 23541, how does this income go into loss
because the investment which the company has done  If this happens, the
company incurs a significant
loss due to which most of the company's
revenue goes into it. So, if we
look at the overall, then the company's revenue, net
revenue, can be seen increasing at a very low rate for the last 10 years,
but a
little problem is coming out here
that when we go towards the company's income,
which is the company's net premium
income, then
what did the company do in the last quarter,
12639 crores, last year
6884 crores, whereas if we look at it now, then the figure is
around 700020 crores, 720 crores, that is, if we
go quarter to quarter, then the
growth is around 45%, yes, there is a
growth of 45%, whereas if we go year to year, then there is a
growth of around 2% year to year,
so that is not considered a big growth, so it is
almost flat over the year, but a
quantum decline of around 45% will be considered a
big decline according to me. Let us
see what the company's expenses are, so let's
talk about the last quarter, last  The
company's profit in the quarter
is 10640. Last year, the company's expenses were also
in loss because the investment itself was
in loss, so the expenses were also in loss, this is 1856 crores,
whereas in the quarter, let's
see what the company's net profit is, so
see how the
dividend was not given in the notes but of 60 paise, so
remember, let's
see the overall profit net profit of the company which comes to the bank, let's talk about the last quarter,
in the last quarter the profit of the company
was around 235 crores,
last year it was 156 crores, if we give it now then it has reached
around 206 crores, so
you have seen the profit of the company giving,
but if we look at the year to year,
you can also see a good increase from year to year
and why is there an increase because you all
know that there was a little problem in the investment of the company, due to which
you have seen the profit of the company decreasing,
but one more thing I would
like to highlight here, the company
also made a profit of 178 crores in this quarter  There has been a
profit of 178 from the fund in Future and UPPCL Appropriation, so
according to me, if you summarize this number
because you will not be able to understand the complex numbers
properly, so let me explain it to you, then
you have seen the net income of the company falling,
which according to me is wrong, if the
net income is flat for the company, then that too is nothing special overall, the
profit of the company is also
given, that was seen, according to me the
numbers are seen going a little weak, let's see
how the market will do,
but I saw the numbers which were a little less than the most, so that's all
for today, if you
like the video then like it and also
subscribe to my channel,
thank you